[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ようちえん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Дит. садок"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しょくぶつえん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Ботанічний сад"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ゆうえんち' read in word?",
        "answer": "Парк розваг"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おてら' read in word?",
        "answer": "Храм (буддійський)"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'やおや' read in word?",
        "answer": "Овочевий"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'たいいくかん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Спортзал"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'たいしかん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Посольство"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しょうぼうしょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Пожежна станція"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けいさつしょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відділ поліції"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はくぶつかん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Музей"
    }
]
